I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Huh?
Did you get the shell?
（男性：英語）
〈薬莢(やっきょう)は届いたかい？〉
（エディ：英語）〈誰だ？〉
You?
（男性）〈大人しく質問に
答えれば それでいい〉
Just answer my question.
It'll be all good.
〈エディ・リーが死ぬと
大勢の白人が悲しむんだろ？〉
All the white dudes will be sad
if Eddy Lee's dead, right?
〈俺にとっちゃ
どうでもいいことだがね〉
For me, I don't give a fuck!
〈誰の？〉
Who told you to do this?
ヘイ ヘイ！
Hey! Hey!
〈質問するのはこっちなんだよ〉
I'm asking you!
〈貴様が盗んだモノはどこだ！〉
Where the fuck is this thing you stole?
（竜介(りゅうすけ)：英語）〈何だって？〉
Say what?
（竜介）
〈エディ お前 大丈夫なのか？〉
Whoa Eddy! Are you all right?
（エディ）〈ああ〉
Yeah. He took off right when
the security guys came in.
〈セキュリティーが入ってきて
ヤツは逃げ出したよ〉
（竜介）〈そうか〉
I see. You are still lucky.
〈よかった〉
〈ヤツにバレたんだ〉
I knew it! He found out everything.
（竜介）〈いや 絶対に
バレないはずだ！〉
Can't be. How could he find out?
〈映画が完成したんだ〉
Ray, the movie's done.
〈ジムが監督した
俺たちのツアームービーだよ〉
Our tour movie, that Jim directed.
イェー…
Yeah?
（エディ）〈先週から何度か
試写をやってるんだ〉
Yeah, they've been previewing it
a couple of times last week...
〈まさか〉
What?
Yeah, I told Jim to cut out
the scene of me playing, "Lucille."
（エディ）〈ルシールを弾くシーンを
カットしてほしいって—〉
〈ジムに頼んだんだけど
ヤツもアーティストだからな〉
You know, he's an artist.
〈そうか〉
Well...
Yeah, it was the uh...
It was the scene of Koyuki.
〈コユキの歌が—〉
〈やけに印象的なシーンなんだ〉
You know, singing really, really good.
"Live 16 'Indies'"
（コユキ）ま また 来ます
I'll come again!
（店員）何ですかね～
What's with that kid?
あのガキ 毎日 来ちゃ
ニタニタして キモいっすよ
He comes in everyday, smiling.
Gives me the creeps.
（高野(たかの)）ああ 何でも
テレキャスターを見ると—
I hear if you keep staring at a Telecaster,
it helps you endure even hard labor.
過酷な労働にも
耐えられるんだってさ
へえ～
Oh...
でも—
But...
早くしないと 売れちゃうよ
He'd better make up his mind
or it'll be sold.
（料理人）おい！ おい！
Hey! Hey!
Where're the spring rolls?!
（料理人）春巻き まだか？
Oh sorry!
（コユキ）あっ すいません
Hey Tanaka! The dumplings are overdone.
（店長）おい 田中
天心が焦げすぎだよ
お客様から クレーム出てる
I just got a complaint.
（コユキ）あっ すいません
-I'm sorry!
-Hey, spring rolls!
おい 春巻き！
（コユキ）はいっ
Right!
おい 田中 スープの
つぎ方が悪いって—
Hey Tanaka!
You didn't ladle the soup carefully!
The same customer is complaining!
同じお客から
またクレーム出てるぞ
ああ すいませ～ん
I'm sorry.
おかしいな ちゃんと
やってるんだけどな
Strange...I'm doing it properly.
My goodness!
-How many times must I complain
before you get things right?!
-I'm so sorry.
（斎藤(さいとう)）な～んど 言ったら
この店は ちゃんとした—
サ～ビスが で～きるんだよ
まったく もう～
（斎藤）あ～ も こんなものでねえ
お金をもらおうなんて—
-How can I pay for this?
-Huh? It's Saito-san...
（コユキ）あ！ な 何で
斎藤さんが…
どういう 神経してんだ
ええ～？
（斎藤）
いや～ ホント てっきり—
I thought they'd give me a free meal.
タダにしてくれると
思ったんだけどなあ～
チーッ 実に セコい店だ
-What a stingy shop.
-You're the stingy one!
（コユキ）
セコいのは あんただよ
I'm counting on you for Tuesday.
じゃあ うちのほうは
火曜日ね 頼むよっ
配達も どっさりあるしね
I have lots of deliveries.
ふらりと お風呂にでも
行ってみようかなあ
I guess I'll go to the bathhouse.
リエリエ ああ リエリエ
リエリエっと…
Ouch!
（益岡(ますおか)）いった～い
Maybe I'll go meet that girl who works
at the doughnut shop next door.
隣のドーナツ屋の面接
受けてみよっかな～ へへッ
コラ サボってねえで
仕事しろお！
Hey! Quit loafing and get back to work!
Oh, sorry!
（コユキ）だあ！ すいません！
He's so cool!
（女子生徒１）
んも～ 超カッコいいよね～
Well, too bad! Yoshito belongs to me!
（女子生徒２）ダメダメ～
ヨシトは 私のもの
No way! Yoshito's mine!
（女子生徒３）ええっ
ヨシトは私の～
-Hey!
-Excuse me!
（女子生徒１）
ちょっと放してよ！
（コユキ）あ それって…
"Yoshito Morozumi"
Is this guy popular?
（コユキ）
この人って人気あんの？
Is this guy popular?
Are you serious? You don't
watch TV on Mondays at 8?
えっ マジ？ 田中君
月８(げっぱち)のドラマ 見てないの？
It's a sad drama about
a short-distance runner.
短距離ランナーの孤独だよ？
ハルカ 超 好きなんですけど～
I sooo love it!
Yoshito plays a young guy in
a wheelchair. And he's awesome.
ヨシト君は 車椅子の少年役で
かなり ブレイク寸前だよお～
Oh...
ふ～ん
いやっ きょうは 入ったねえ
Good, we had a good crowd tonight.
I'm totally beat!
（女性店員１）
ホント～ 疲れた～
-You'll get paid nicely tonight.
-Really?
（店長）こりゃあ 大入り 出るよ
（女性店員２）ええ マジですか～
Hey Tanaka-kun!
（女性店員１）お～い 田中君
There's a female customer
named Minami asking for you.
南って女の子のお客さんが
呼んでるぞっ
えっ 真帆(まほ)？
Huh? Maho?
She's quite cute.
なかなか カワイイ子じゃん
Your girlfriend?
コレか？
（コユキ）いやあ 違いますよ
No...nothing like that.
Hi!
（真帆）ウイーッス
Hey, doesn't that boy look familiar?
ねえ あの男の子
見たことないか？
Huh?
（女性店員２）え～？
-He's the one in the drama.
-A-And that water commercial!
あ～ ドラマの人だ
み 水のＣＭに出てた…
-Ryusuke told me you worked here.
-Oh...
ここ 竜介から聞いてきたんだ～
へえ
You sure are working hard.
なかなか 頑張ってるみたいじゃん
Nah...Not really.
いや まだ 何か…
Oh yeah, let me introduce you...
This is one of my classmates, Yoshito.
あ そうだ 紹介するね
クラスメートのヨシト
We met once in Mi-chan's shop.
You're on TV, right? That's awesome.
前に ミッちゃんの店で会ったよ
ドラマとか出てるんでしょ？
すごいなあ
Hey Maho...this guy looks so dirty.
（ヨシト）おい 真帆 こいつ
すげえ 汚い格好だけど—
You sure the food here is okay?
ここの食いもん 大丈夫？
-Koyuki, are you free on Monday?
-Why?
ねえ コユキは月曜 空いてる？
何で？
It's Christine's birthday party.
クリスティーンの
バースデーパーティー やるんだ
I wondered if you could come.
コユキも来ないかなって
思ってさあ
ああ クリスティーン…
Christine?
What?
（ヨシト：英語）〈パーティーは
学校の友達だけでやるんだろ？〉
I thought we were gonna have this party
only with friends from school.
（真帆：英語）〈いいじゃん！〉
Why not? It's always more fun
with more people.
〈大勢いたほうが楽しいもん〉
What do you mean?
We already have enough people.
（ヨシト）
〈もう十分呼んでるじゃないか〉
Why are you so unhappy about it?
（真帆）〈大勢のほうがいいよ〉
すっごい バイリンガルだぞ
-Wow! They're bilingual!
-And she's so pretty.
あの子 マジ きれいな顔してる～
They were eating the 5000-yen course.
（バイト１）あいつら
5,000円のコース食ってたぜ
Hope they have money.
（バイト２）
チェッ やってらんね～
And I can't even speak English.
俺なんか 英語も
しゃべれないしさ
Hey kid!
おい 小僧
Quit daydreaming!
チンタラ やってんじゃね～
（コユキ）うわああ！
I'm sorry!
すいませ～ん
（千葉(ちば)）アハハ いや ホント
ありがとうございました ハハッ
No, thank you so much! Good-bye!
Every label turned us down?
（平(たいら)）
どこのレーベルも ダメなのか？
Our self-produced CD is a total disaster.
全滅だよ 俺たちの 自主製作ＣＤ
うああ～ん
（サク）んん あれだけ
頑張って 作ったのに…
We worked so hard on it.
Ran's influence was worse than I expected.
思った以上だな 蘭(らん)の影響力は
No one would come right out and say it,
but I could feel Ran's influence.
ああ どこも はっきりとは
話してくれないが—
蘭の 分厚い壁を
感じるぜえ フゥ～
Can we break through it? With our power?
たたき割れるのか？
俺たちの力で
Ran...
蘭…
Lift up your heavy ass, now
（BECK(ベック)の曲）
If you take off that stiff head
You'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
-Well...the sound is still amateur...
-You just have to Stage Dive or Die
（蘭）まあ しょせん音は
アマチュアレベルだが—
-but I do feel some good vibes from it
-Mind blower, a shower of sweat
光るものは感じるぜ
even with a name like Beck.
BECKっていうバンド名は
おいといてな
However...
（蘭）だが こいつらが
メジャーデビューすることはない！
these guys will never make a major debut.
It's unfortunate,
残念だがな
but anyone who crosses me
will be destroyed!
俺をコケにしたヤローは
葬るだけだ！
Ran-san...
（栄二(えいじ)）蘭さん…
Eiji, in this world,
only the strongest survive.
栄二！ この世界は
強い者だけが 生き残るんだぞ
In this world, power is everything.
（栄二）
この世界は 力がすべてなんだ
And Ran-san has it.
蘭さんは それを持っている
And someone powerless like me,
just has to be smart and get around it.
力のない俺は
うまく立ち回るしかない
That's the reality.
それが現実だ
But Ryusuke, I'll become successful
no matter what I have to do.
でもな 竜介
俺はどんな
きたねえことしても—
サクセスをつかむ
Ah...On the sixteenth?
（真帆）〈16日？〉
I can't. I got a red flag.
〈ダメだよ〉
〈BECKのライブだもん〉
Come on, Maho. My father's friend
opened an Italian restaurant.
カモーン 真帆
〈オヤジの友達が始めた
イタメシ屋の夜景—〉
You know, in nighttime,
the view from there is so great.
〈メチャクチャきれいなんだぜ〉
（真帆）ふんっ！
All right, I'll think about it.
〈じゃ 考えとく〉
Oh, I gotta go to bathroom.
〈私 トイレ…〉
What kind of band is Beck?
（友人：英語）〈BECKって
どんなバンドなんだ？〉
They put their live [performance]
Before anything else.
〈そんなにイイのかよ？〉
〈いつもライブが最優先じゃん〉
Well, I just met the singer.
（ヨシト）〈さっきボーカル
やってるヤツに会ってきた〉
〈で どうよ？〉
And?
He was just a tiny tot.
〈チンケなボーヤだったぜ〉
Yes, hello?
〈もしもし〉
Oh, I dialed the wrong number.
（コユキ）あれ？
ま 間違えました
Oh, it's Koyuki-kun?
ああ コユキ君だろ？
Uh...Yes.
（コユキ）あっ はい
Maho is taking a shower
and can't come to the phone.
真帆のヤツ 今 シャワー
浴びてて 出れないけど—
Anything you want me to tell her?
何か 伝えておこうか？
Oh?
About Monday's party.
ああ それじゃあ
月曜のパーティーって…
Oh, the party...
（ヨシト）ああ パーティーね
Come to the party dressed
like you were invited to a ball.
パーティーは 迎賓館に
招待されたような—
正装で来てほしいな
And don't forget the present for the guest.
もちろん 主賓への
プレゼントもよろしく
And who...
（コユキ）それって…
〈おい 何笑ってんだよ〉
Hey, what're you laughing about?
You're kind, Koyuki.
コユキは優しいね
But you don't seem to like my friends.
でも 私の友達のことは嫌いみたい
It's Christine's birthday party.
クリスティーンの
バースデーパーティー やるんだ
I wondered if you could come.
コユキも来ないかなって
思ってさあ
（男性：英語）〈オイ〉
Hey you! This place is reserved today.
〈きょうは貸し切りだ〉
〈ウロウロしないでくれよ〉
Don't mess around here...please.
うわっ いや…　マイ フレンド
イズ エンジョイ パーティー
Err...no...My friend is enjoy party.
あっ！ ヨシト君！
Ah! Yoshito-kun!
（ヨシト）
あっ 事情が変わっちゃってさ
Sorry, but plans were changed.
Now this party is only for school friends.
きょうのパーティー 学校の
友達だけで やることになったんだ
そんな…
That's...
だから 部外者は
入れないんだ 悪いね
So others can't come in. Sorry.
Oh...
じゃあ これをクリスティーンに
Please give this to Christine then.
Sure.
じゃあなっ ハハッ
See ya!
〈何で？〉
Why?!
〈あいつ 本気にしてさぁ〉
'Cause he really took it serious.
〈マヌケなカッコで
来やがったぜぇ〉
He looked so stupid.
コユキ…！
Koyuki...
（ヨシト）
〈あんなヤツ どーでもいいだろ〉
Hey! He don't give a fuck!
ハァ ハァ…
ああっ テレキャスがない
The Telecaster is gone.
高野さんが
奥で待っててくれって
Takano-san said to wait in the back.
（コユキ）んんっ！
（店員）あっ おいっ！
Hey!
（コユキ）ハァ ハァ…
（店員）おーい 待ってくれ～
Hey! Wait!
ちょっ…　高野さんがあ！
Takano-san wants...
おおい！
Hey!
（コユキ）ハァ ハァ
どっ 泥棒～!!
T-Thief!
Huh?
高野～
Takano...
クラ～ッシュ!!
（コユキ）どわああ！
Crush!
（コユキ）どわっ！ ああ…
（高野）片平(かたひら)さん
どうすか？ そのテレキャス
Katahira-san, how is that Telecaster?
I made lots of adjustments.
いろんなとこ イジってるんですよ
あ 片平…
Katahira...
（片平）おお どらあ
ええ味 出とるがや
Ohh...It's nice. I wanna buy it.
俺 買(こ)うてえ
あっ… ラウド・クライム・
シティーの 片平達也…
Huh? It's Tatsuya Katahira
of Loud Crime City.
Can't do that. This kid's gonna buy it.
ダメですよ この小僧が
買うんですから
倍 払うで
I'll pay you double.
あっ 俺 予約したわけじゃ…
-I didn't reserve it...
-No, Taira asked me.
ダメだよ
俺は 平に頼まれてんだ
Oh...
俺はドラマーだで ギターも
弾いてやらんと かわいそうだろ
I'm a drummer, but I've gotta be nice
and give guitars a chance, too.
ういっしょ
その小僧 買わんかったら
連絡ちょうだい
If that kid doesn't buy it, let me know.
本当にラウドは 今度のライブで
解散しちゃうんですか？
Is Loud really going to disband
after their next live performance?
おうよ 人間
引き際が 肝心だでよ
Yup. You gotta know when to call it quits.
よかったら 見にきて
Come watch us.
（高野）小僧 期限は
月末までだからな いいな？
Kid, the deadline is
the end of the month. Got it?
はいっ！
Yes!
（竜介）へえ～ ラウドの片平とね
Hmm...Katahira of Loud?
Yup...
It's true that Loud
is Japan's top rock band.
（サク）実質 ラウドが日本の
ナンバーワン ロックバンドだよね
（コユキ）
ねえ 見に行こうよ 武道館
Let's go see them at the Budokan.
（平）バーカ もう とっくに
ソールドアウトだよ
Stupid! It was sold out ages ago.
フンッ 俺たちとは えらく違うな
Hah! So different from us.
ラウドだって 初めから
ああだったわけじゃないぜ
Loud wasn't popular from the start.
まずは きょうのライブだよ
Let's just concentrate on today's show.
（千葉）
そうだなあ ライブも大事だ
Right! Live performances are important.
でもな 今の俺たちの問題は ん…
But our problem right now is...
This!
これだっ!!
プレスしたのが300枚
そんで 在庫が210枚
We ordered 300 copies
and we have 210 left.
１人 42枚だ！
That's 42 copies each!
親戚 知人を総動員して
ノルマを達成してくれ!!
Friends, family, anyone you
can think of! Sell them all!
そ そんな 40人なんて
知り合いいないよ
B-But I don't know 40 people!
ノルマが達成できなきゃ
莫大な赤字が残るだけだぞ！
If we don't get rid of these,
we'll end up with a huge debt!
-Oh...
（千葉）
ウイーッス BECKだあ!!
Yo! We're Beck!
こんなに入ってるのに
みんな 声が小せえなあ
It's packed tonight,
but there's not much noise.
彼らが見たいのは
次のバンドだからな
They're all waiting for the next band.
We should pump them up.
この客 ごっそり いただきたいね
One, two...
ワン ツー
Uh!
Yeah!
You open up the door
with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
If you never change
It's probably the last time
I'll use this in a live performance.
I think there is no way
my life fizzle out
（コユキ）たぶん ライブで
使うのは これが最後だ
今まで ありがとう
ホワイトファルコン
Thank you for all this time...
White Falcon.
You open up the door with negative aura
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
When Loud disbands,
Japanese rock will die.
You say future is murky...
（記者）ラウドの解散で
日本のロックは絶滅する
And that's not an understatement.
（記者）…と言っても 決して
言いすぎじゃないと思うんです
（片平）ふ～ん
It's fact that Loud has carried
the Japanese scene on its shoulders.
事実 ラウドが日本の
ロックシーンを—
引っ張ってきたじゃないですか
Really?
そうか
And there's been no band
that can compare to Loud.
そして ラウドを
継承するようなバンドは—
まったく出ていない
Our gas ran out.
ガソリンが 切れたんだ
Huh?
We can't run anymore.
俺らはもう 走れなくなったんだで
You must know...
あんたは分かるだろうけど
音楽シーンには—
In the music scene,
something's always evolving.
周期みてえなもんがある
Somewhere right now, there's an
unknown band making great music.
たぶん 今もさ どっかで
誰も見たことねえような—
すげえバンドが
演奏してるんだわ
Is there such a band?
（記者）そんなバンドが…
No one knows about them yet,
（片平）そいつらのこと 今は
誰も 知んねえけど—
but they'll come onto the next music scene
次のシーンに出てきてさ—
and let us listen to the real McCoy.
本物の音を
聞かしてくれるはずだで
（片平）ほんじゃ
See ya!
Katahira-san!
片平さ～ん
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
（ミッちゃん）フフッ なかなか
聞けるようになったじゃねえか—
He's gotten pretty good...that kid.
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
小僧のギター へへへッ
Go against headwind
or ride on the tailwind.
Game is in your hands.
How do you play?
Follow your brainstorm!
（社長：英語）
〈そのＣＤ 買える？〉
Could I get the CD?
Uh, yes. The band's called Beck.
〈はい！〉
〈BECKでいいんですか？〉
Yes, a good band.
（社長）
〈ああ 良いバンドだ〉
Especially guitar.
〈ギターがイカスね〉
Yes!
〈はい〉
The president of an
Indies label in Chicago?
（竜介）シカゴのインディー
レーベルの社長？
Yup! It seems he just walked in by chance.
うん 本当に たまたま
入ったらしいけどね
Well, there are lots
of foreigners around here.
（平）
ここら 結構 外国人 多いもんな
Hmm...
Sun Factory Record...Frank Albin.
〈サンファクトリーレコードの〉
〈フランク・アルビンだって〉
（千葉）うーん それって全然
聞いたこと ねえんだけど
Never heard of it.
-Is it all right?
-He seemed nice.
大丈夫？
うーん いい人… だったよ
All right. Cheers!
（竜介）よおし 乾杯だ
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
I bought bags for the dog's poo.
（千葉）
犬の ウンコ袋を買いました
"Live 17 'Three Days'"
Why do I hafta walk Beck?! Ryusuke!
何でベックの散歩を
俺がやんなきゃ—
いけねえんだよっ
竜介～！